<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Filler | Coffee-Ops]]></title>
  <link href="http://coffee-ops.github.io/blog/categories/filler/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://coffee-ops.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2014-10-16T12:02:12-05:00</updated>
  <id>http://coffee-ops.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[The Coffee-Ops Community]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Post]]></title>
    <link href="http://coffee-ops.github.io/blog/2014/10/15/new-post/"/>
    <updated>2014-10-15T16:17:31-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://coffee-ops.github.io/blog/2014/10/15/new-post</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>That strong extraction mocha body decaffeinated java ristretto, java variety, est, caffeine, dripper, kopi-luwak a, whipped galão cinnamon aroma trifecta galão latte doppio. Brewed est sit white crema cultivar breve turkish grinder half and half est dripper, aromatic froth grinder, flavour aftertaste, affogato whipped roast shop affogato eu plunger pot. Aromatic grounds, dark, extra, arabica, kopi-luwak, barista cup siphon skinny ristretto fair trade galão affogato, rich white latte, americano at qui cortado iced. Half and half cream arabica french press id, mocha bar that bar skinny, est cup barista lungo extra grounds.</p>

<p>Cream at crema carajillo black doppio mazagran, con panna, ut eu sugar wings fair trade that rich id saucer shop so foam steamed. Coffee, single origin, filter, viennese caramelization siphon breve a, seasonal, as, mazagran decaffeinated, doppio, plunger pot, extra, acerbic single origin strong doppio body. Robusta wings extra, flavour latte wings medium, a doppio ut french press fair trade breve caramelization grinder acerbic plunger pot single origin aftertaste. Body skinny, crema, body, brewed whipped arabica siphon, fair trade, eu aromatic, milk ut instant arabica steamed java filter.</p>

<p>Cup organic breve skinny frappuccino skinny galão, breve in irish, est galão decaffeinated eu aged. Affogato con panna at robust, acerbic, sugar single shot strong americano sweet acerbic wings that grinder dark acerbic. Seasonal, so coffee, doppio, siphon et filter, single origin roast plunger pot aroma filter, grinder crema sweet black doppio irish. Irish a acerbic coffee, percolator french press breve white crema body milk et dripper roast iced instant single origin organic breve pumpkin spice macchiato cream.</p>

<p>Stolen from <a href="http://coffeeipsum.com/">coffeeipsum</a></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
